(Watch on www.kisskh.xyz Support Admin)
(شاهد على www.kisskh.xyz دعم الإدارة)
Go!
يذهب!
Whoa!
يا إلهي!
Stop!
قف!
Damn it!
عليك اللعنة!
Drop the bag!
أسقط الحقيبة!
Oh, shit!
يا للقرف!
Come here!
تعال الى هنا!
Start the car!
شغّل السيارة!
Hurry up! Hurry. Run faster.
أسرع! أسرع. اركض أسرع.
Hurry, hurry! Come on!
أسرعوا، أسرعوا! هيا!
Start the car!
شغّل السيارة!
- Bastards. - Run faster!
- أوغاد. - اركضوا أسرع!
Hurry!
عجل!
Please hurry up.
أرجوك أسرع.
Come on. Door. Door. Door. Come on, let's go!
هيا بنا. الباب. الباب. الباب. هيا بنا، لنذهب!
God dammit.
اللعنة!
BLOODHOUNDS
كلاب الصيد
People borrowing from Kim Myeong-gil is way more than we thought.
إن عدد الأشخاص الذين يستعيرون من كيم ميونغ غيل أكبر بكثير مما كنا نعتقد.
They all enter the bar in one-hour intervals.
يدخلون جميعاً إلى الحانة على فترات زمنية مدتها ساعة واحدة.
Some of them in official police vehicles.
بعضهم في سيارات الشرطة الرسمية.
I don't know his name,
لا أعرف اسمه،
but there was also a professional baseball player.
لكن كان هناك أيضاً لاعب بيسبول محترف.
Yeah, well, seems he's expanded his reach.
نعم، يبدو أنه وسّع نطاق نفوذه.
I knew it that Myeong-gil was an ex-convict.
كنت أعرف أن ميونغ غيل كان سجينًا سابقًا.
He begged for my help.
لقد توسل إليّ طلباً للمساعدة.
He said all he wanted was a fresh start.
قال إنه كل ما يريده هو بداية جديدة.
And like an idiot…
ومثل الأحمق...
I fell for it.
لقد انخدعت.
After Myeong-gil screwed me,
بعد أن خانني ميونغ غيل،
I went into hiding with Mr. Oh.
ذهبت للاختباء مع السيد أوه.
That's when I heard rumors that he'd started a company
حينها سمعت شائعات بأنه قد أسس شركة
using the money and bonds he had stolen from me.
باستخدام الأموال والسندات التي سرقها مني.
I should've taken care of him a long time ago.
كان ينبغي عليّ أن أعتني به منذ زمن طويل.
I taught him everything.
لقد علمته كل شيء.
I didn't have the courage.
لم تكن لدي الشجاعة.
I wish I would've gained some by now.
أتمنى لو كنت قد اكتسبت بعض الوزن حتى الآن.
I shouldn't have stopped you from going after him
ما كان ينبغي لي أن أمنعك من ملاحقته
and giving him what he deserved.
وإعطائه ما يستحقه.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I was too afraid I'd lose you as well.
كنت خائفًا جدًا من أن أفقدك أنت أيضًا.
You've always…
لطالما كنتَ...
cared for me and protected me like I was family.
لقد اعتنى بي وحماني كما لو كنت فرداً من عائلتهم.
I'm always…
أنا دائماً...
…ready to lay my life on the line for you anytime you need it, sir.
...مستعد للتضحية بحياتي من أجلك في أي وقت تحتاج إليه يا سيدي.
I know you are.
أعلم أنك كذلك.
And I'm sorry.
وأنا آسف.
Hello.
مرحبًا.
Okay.
تمام.
Come on back.
تفضل بالعودة.
So, uh, it seems the kids just got jumped
إذن، يبدو أن الأطفال قد تعرضوا للهجوم.
while they were moving all the money.
بينما كانوا ينقلون كل الأموال.
- Are they hurt? - No, they didn't mention it.
- هل أصيبوا بأذى؟ - لا، لم يذكروا ذلك.
But, uh,
لكن، آه،
they said they lost the money from the safe.
قالوا إنهم فقدوا المال من الخزنة.
Are they hurt or not?
هل أصيبوا أم لا؟
I think they're all right.
أعتقد أنهم جميعاً على حق.
They also… tied one of them up but didn't want to finish him off.
كما أنهم... قاموا بتقييد أحدهم لكنهم لم يرغبوا في القضاء عليه.
Now what?
والآن ماذا؟
When an ER receives a patient that was injured doing something illegal…
عندما يستقبل قسم الطوارئ مريضاً أصيب أثناء قيامه بعمل غير قانوني...
…the doctors are obligated to call the police.
...الأطباء ملزمون باستدعاء الشرطة.
That's why I used to have surgeons of my own
لهذا السبب كان لدي جراحون خاصون بي
ready to operate at all times.
جاهز للعمل في جميع الأوقات.
I'm pretty sure Myeong-gil must have a similar arrangement.
أنا متأكد تماماً من أن ميونغ غيل لديها ترتيب مماثل.
I'll go get Du-yeong. He's gonna find him fast.
سأذهب لأحضر دو يونغ. سيجده بسرعة.
Good job.
أحسنت.
Hey.
يا.
Uh, yeah.
أجل، صحيح.
Get some sleep, okay? Come to the restaurant tomorrow.
خذ قسطاً من الراحة، حسناً؟ تعال إلى المطعم غداً.
What? Uh, what for?
ماذا؟ همم، لماذا؟
For food.
للطعام.
Oh.
أوه.
Okay?
تمام؟
I don't usually eat lunch.
لا أتناول الغداء عادةً.
- You will. - Yeah.
- ستفعل. - نعم.
Go on.
هيا.
Hey.
يا.
You okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
We lost all the money in the safe. I'm really sorry.
لقد فقدنا كل الأموال الموجودة في الخزنة. أنا آسف حقاً.
But you're not hurt anywhere, right?
لكنك لست مصابًا في أي مكان، أليس كذلك؟
Oh.
أوه.
No.
لا.
That's all that matters.
هذا كل ما يهم.
Oh. I… I have more boxes to move. You should sleep.
أوه. لديّ... لديّ المزيد من الصناديق لنقلها. يجب أن تنام.
Hyeong-ju, are you sure you're not hurt?
هيونغ جو، هل أنت متأكد من أنك لست مصابًا؟
Yeah.
نعم.
It's not that I didn't pay them back, but this guy just came in…
ليس الأمر أنني لم أسدد لهم المبلغ، ولكن هذا الرجل دخل للتو...
In-beom is going to be fine,
إن-بيوم سيكون بخير،
but his eardrum is busted.
لكن طبلة أذنه ممزقة.
I got a license plate. I'll run it through tomorrow.
حصلت على لوحة ترخيص. سأقوم بفحصها غداً.
What do you mean "tomorrow"?
ماذا تقصد بكلمة "غداً"؟
That's when the officers we pay are on duty.
هذا هو الوقت الذي يكون فيه الضباط الذين ندفع لهم رواتبهم في الخدمة.
Watch your tone with me.
انتبه لنبرة صوتك معي.
Don't push me.
لا تدفعني.
Ah, shit.
آه، يا إلهي.
If it's an unregistered vehicle or fake plates,
إذا كانت المركبة غير مسجلة أو تحمل لوحات مزيفة،
is it possible to track it with the security cameras?
هل من الممكن تتبعه باستخدام كاميرات المراقبة؟
It's definitely possible, but it would take us a little while.
من المؤكد أن ذلك ممكن، لكنه سيستغرق منا بعض الوقت.
License plates can be looked up on the police Intranet.
يمكن البحث عن لوحات ترخيص السيارات على شبكة الشرطة الداخلية.
But if we're talking about getting security footage,
لكن إذا كنا نتحدث عن الحصول على لقطات كاميرات المراقبة،
that's a different story. We'd have to… be able to get inside control centers,
هذا موضوع آخر. سيتعين علينا... أن نكون قادرين على الدخول إلى مراكز التحكم،
and I would need to pay off the right kinds of people.
وسأحتاج إلى دفع الأموال للأشخاص المناسبين.
Money is not an issue.
المال ليس مشكلة.
Just get it done quickly.
أنجز الأمر بسرعة.
Yes.
نعم.
I want you to find out who owns the building.
أريدك أن تكتشف من يملك المبنى.
If it's Choi, you need to get his home address.
إذا كان المقصود هو تشوي، فأنت بحاجة إلى الحصول على عنوان منزله.
Yeah.
نعم.
You can go now.
يمكنك الذهاب الآن.
Let me talk to Jang-do.
دعني أتحدث إلى جانغ-دو.
Sir?
سيد؟
You heard me.
لقد سمعتني.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Beom,
بيوم،
why do you think they left him there?
لماذا تعتقد أنهم تركوه هناك؟
Is it because they had run out of time?
هل السبب هو نفاد الوقت؟
Jang-do. Jang-do, huh?
جانغ-دو. جانغ-دو، هاه؟
You're thinking far too positively right now.
أنت تفكر بإيجابية مفرطة في الوقت الحالي.
Think negatively for a change.
فكّر بشكل سلبي هذه المرة.
Try to understand.
حاول أن تفهم.
Those bastards are trying to kill you.
هؤلاء الأوغاد يحاولون قتلك.
You should allow that idea to drive your thoughts.
ينبغي أن تسمح لتلك الفكرة بأن توجه أفكارك.
So why'd they leave him there?
فلماذا تركوه هناك؟
They're planning to track him.
إنهم يخططون لتعقبه.
Okay then.
حسناً إذاً.
We need to get more men and put them at the hospital.
نحتاج إلى جلب المزيد من الرجال ووضعهم في المستشفى.
Yes.
نعم.
And we need to follow Jun-min.
ونحن بحاجة إلى اتباع جون مين.
Why? Did he do something wrong?
لماذا؟ هل فعل شيئاً خاطئاً؟
Uh, I told you to think negatively about this.
أجل، لقد طلبت منك أن تفكر بشكل سلبي في هذا الأمر.
Mr. Choi may have info on him.
قد يكون لدى السيد تشوي معلومات عنه.
Ah.
آه.
Jun-min is just a coward.
جون مين مجرد جبان.
He's turned way too easily.
لقد انقلب عليه بسهولة بالغة.
It'll be very obvious.
سيكون الأمر واضحاً جداً.
One look at his face, and he just gives everything away, huh?
نظرة واحدة إلى وجهه، ويكشف كل شيء، أليس كذلك؟
Sir.
سيد.
All right now.
حسناً الآن.
Beom is just a small fry here.
بيوم مجرد شخص عادي هنا.
So Lee Du-yeong is our man.
إذن لي دو يونغ هو رجلنا.
He's got a bike.
لديه دراجة.
That's who they'll send to tail him.
هؤلاء هم الذين سيرسلونهم لمراقبته.
Yeah.
نعم.
Block the streets and trap him.
أغلقوا الشوارع واحاصروه.
Should be fun.
سيكون الأمر ممتعاً.
Oh!
أوه!
Did you sleep well, sir?
هل نمت جيداً يا سيدي؟
Did you get any sleep?
هل نمتَ قليلاً؟
Yeah.
نعم.
You got back so late. You should rest now.
لقد عدت متأخراً جداً. يجب أن ترتاح الآن.
I got plenty of sleep, but thank you.
لقد نمتُ جيداً، ولكن شكراً لك.
Ah, Gun-woo,
آه، غون وو،
I've been meaning to talk to you, actually.
كنت أنوي التحدث إليك، في الحقيقة.
Oh.
أوه.
Hyeon-ju, uh… You may have noticed she always has a bit of an edge to here.
هيون جو، آه... ربما لاحظتِ أنها دائماً ما تكون حادة بعض الشيء هنا.
Oh.
أوه.
I think that's the reason why she acts a little cold at times.
أعتقد أن هذا هو السبب في أنها تتصرف ببرود بعض الشيء في بعض الأحيان.
Ah.
آه.
But she seems to have softened considerably
لكن يبدو أنها قد خففت من حدتها بشكل ملحوظ.
since meeting you and Woo-jin.
منذ أن التقيت بك أنت ووو جين.
For that, you have my gratitude.
لذلك، لك مني كل الشكر.
We really enjoyed working with Hyeon-ju.
لقد استمتعنا حقاً بالعمل مع هيون جو.
Oh, very good.
أوه، جيد جداً.
So, the money I paid you in advance,
إذن، المال الذي دفعته لك مقدماً،
it's gone.
لقد اختفى.
Oh, so… where did the money go then?
أوه، إذن... أين ذهبت الأموال؟
I meant to say that we're even now.
كنت أقصد أن نقول إننا متعادلون الآن.
Oh, why?
أوه، لماذا؟
Do you have any idea how much money you managed to recover?
هل لديك أي فكرة عن مقدار الأموال التي تمكنت من استردادها؟
Uh, well…
حسنًا...
I'm going to give you a nice bonus for a safe transport.
سأقدم لك مكافأة جيدة مقابل النقل الآمن.
Oh, uh…
أوه، همم...
I'd like to pay it back by putting my fair share of work, sir.
أود أن أردّ الجميل من خلال القيام بنصيبي العادل من العمل، سيدي.
You've already done your share.
لقد قمت بالفعل بدورك.
You three managed to retrieve a considerable sum.
لقد تمكنتم أنتم الثلاثة من استرداد مبلغ كبير.
So from this moment, you're not indebted to me anymore.
من هذه اللحظة، لم تعد مديناً لي.
Get your mom and go open a new café somewhere nice.
اصطحب والدتك وافتح مقهى جديداً في مكان جميل.
I'll make all the necessary investments.
سأقوم بجميع الاستثمارات اللازمة.
Thank you so much, Mr. Choi.
شكراً جزيلاً لك يا سيد تشوي.
I want to help you catch Kim Myeong-gil
أريد مساعدتك في القبض على كيم ميونغ غيل
I'll do that until the very end.
سأفعل ذلك حتى النهاية.
You've been very helpful.
لقد كنتَ مفيداً للغاية.
I know that, but I'd like to see it to the very end.
أعلم ذلك، لكنني أود أن أراه حتى النهاية.
Why?
لماذا؟
To repay my debt.
لسداد ديني.
You've done enough already.
لقد فعلت ما يكفي بالفعل.
It's not enough in my book, sir.
هذا لا يكفي في رأيي يا سيدي.
It's not over until it's over for real.
لن ينتهي الأمر حتى ينتهي فعلاً.
Yeah.
نعم.
It's not over till it's over for real.
لم ينته الأمر حتى ينتهي فعلاً.
We should have a drink sometime soon.
ينبغي أن نتناول مشروباً معاً قريباً.
Oh, I don't really drink, unfortunately.
أوه، للأسف أنا لا أشرب الكحول.
Huh.
هاه.
I'll be more than happy to pour your drinks, sir.
سأكون سعيداً جداً بتقديم مشروباتك يا سيدي.
- Go on. - Oh, okay.
- أكمل. - حسناً.
Use wasabi and soy sauce.
استخدم الوسابي وصلصة الصويا.
Mm.
مم.
Wild caught.
تم اصطيادها في البرية.
You see, farmed halibut have a lot of fat in their fins that can be too heavy.
كما ترى، يحتوي سمك الهلبوت المستزرع على الكثير من الدهون في زعانفه والتي قد تكون ثقيلة للغاية.
But wild ones like this have all that fat evenly distributed.
لكن الأنواع البرية مثل هذه تحتوي على كل تلك الدهون موزعة بالتساوي.
It's such a clean and exquisite flavor.
إنها نكهة نقية ورائعة للغاية.
I can still taste it.
ما زلت أستطيع تذوقه.
And it's aged to perfection.
وقد تم تقطيره إلى درجة الكمال.
Huh.
هاه.
You? An expert?
أنت؟ خبير؟
Oh…
أوه…
I was a restaurant YouTuber back in the day,
كنتُ في الماضي من مُنشئي محتوى المطاعم على يوتيوب.
but my channel didn't get enough subscribers, so I quit.
لكن قناتي لم تحصل على عدد كافٍ من المشتركين، لذلك توقفت عن النشر.
This was my first time having it cut long.
كانت هذه أول مرة أقص فيها شعري طويلاً.
It wraps around your mouth like a whip.
يلتف حول فمك كالسوط.
That was the best halibut I've ever had, sir.
كان ذلك أفضل سمك هلبوت تناولته على الإطلاق يا سيدي.
Love it.
أحبها.
That was amazing.
كان ذلك مذهلاً.
Hey, I'm a hustler.
مرحباً، أنا شخصٌ طموحٌ ومثابر.
I'll subscribe.
سأشترك.
- I told you it's over. - Oh.
- قلت لك انتهى الأمر. - أوه.
You kids went through a lot.
لقد مررتم بالكثير يا أطفال.
That's why I wanted to treat you.
لهذا السبب أردت أن أعالجك.
- Thank you, sir. - Thank you.
- شكراً لك سيدي. - شكراً لك.
What do you plan to do now?
ما الذي تنوي فعله الآن؟
Well, kill the big guy.
حسناً، اقتل الرجل الضخم.
Then catch the one that looks like a wildcat.
ثم أمسك بالذي يشبه القط البري.
That one is Kim Myeong-gil's cleanup crew.
هذا هو فريق التنظيف التابع لكيم ميونغ غيل.
He's the one they send around buying people's silence
هو الشخص الذي يرسلونه لشراء صمت الناس
and threatening their lives whenever it's needed.
وتهديد حياتهم كلما دعت الحاجة.
We'll fuck him up.
سنؤدبه تأديباً شديداً.
And then he's going to lead us to where the bodies are buried.
ثم سيقودنا إلى حيث دُفنت الجثث.
Then we'll have Kim Myeong-gil.
ثم سيكون لدينا كيم ميونغ غيل.
- Then Smile Capital is over. - That's right.
- إذن انتهى برنامج سمايل كابيتال. - هذا صحيح.
Well, what do we do if we don't find any bodies?
حسنًا، ماذا نفعل إذا لم نجد أي جثث؟
Well, we can find a murder weapon or maybe some security footage.
حسناً، يمكننا العثور على أداة الجريمة أو ربما بعض لقطات كاميرات المراقبة.
Here.
هنا.
As for the yellowtail,
أما بالنسبة لسمك ذيل أصفر،
the age--
العمر--
Oh, sorry I'm late.
أوه، آسف على التأخير.
- Sit, sit. Sit, sit. - Took your time.
- اجلس، اجلس. اجلس، اجلس. - لقد أخذت وقتك.
Lee Du-yeong. Nice to meet you. Pound this.
لي دو يونغ. تشرفت بلقائك. اضرب هذا.
- Kim Gun-woo, sir. - Uh-huh.
- كيم غون وو، سيدي. - أوه-هاه.
- Hong Woo-jin. - Oh, boxer fists. Hello.
- هونغ وو جين. - أوه، لكمات الملاكم. مرحباً.
I went to the underpass that day.
ذهبت إلى النفق في ذلك اليوم.
I went over there as soon as your grandfather called me,
ذهبت إلى هناك فور أن اتصل بي جدك.
but I got there late.
لكنني وصلت متأخراً.
Then I saw those goons lying on the ground and thought,
ثم رأيت أولئك الأوغاد ملقين على الأرض وفكرت،
"These guys can fight."
"هؤلاء الرجال يجيدون القتال."
Remember when you wanted to be a boxing champion back then?
أتذكر عندما كنت تحلم بأن تصبح بطلاً في الملاكمة؟
- That was a long time ago. - What is it?
- كان ذلك منذ زمن بعيد. - ما الأمر؟
We got a hit.
لقد حققنا نجاحاً.
Who?
من؟
The sales director.
مدير المبيعات.
Let's talk in the back.
لنتحدث في الخلف.
What? Why? They're coming with us.
ماذا؟ لماذا؟ إنهم قادمون معنا.
What are you talking about?
عن ماذا تتحدث؟
- What's the problem? - It'll make them all accomplices.
- ما المشكلة؟ - سيجعلهم ذلك جميعاً شركاء في الجريمة.
Hey, they're the ones who wanted in.
هم من أرادوا المشاركة.
Listen, once you have a record, boxing days are over. Got it?
اسمع، بمجرد أن تسجل رقماً قياسياً، تنتهي أيام الملاكمة. هل فهمت؟
Yeah.
نعم.
Why are you fighting Kim Myeong-gil, Mr. Hwang?
لماذا تقاتل كيم ميونغ غيل يا سيد هوانغ؟
I'm here to finally avenge our boys.
أنا هنا لأنتقم أخيراً لأبنائنا.
But you could die fighting him.
لكنك قد تموت وأنت تقاتله.
Aren't you… afraid?
ألا تشعر بالخوف؟
What I'm really afraid of is not managing to kill the fucker.
ما أخشاه حقاً هو عدم تمكني من قتل ذلك الوغد.
Okay, and what about you two?
حسناً، وماذا عنكما أنتما؟
- I'm in. - Me too.
- أنا موافق. - وأنا أيضاً.
Why?
لماذا؟
Because Kim Myeong-gil is a bad man.
لأن كيم ميونغ غيل رجل سيء.
My family would have been ruined without the help of Mr. Choi.
لولا مساعدة السيد تشوي، لكانت عائلتي قد دُمرت .
I'm only good at fighting,
أنا أجيد القتال فقط،
so I'll help however I can.
لذا سأساعد بكل ما أستطيع.
Same here.
نفس الشيء هنا.
These two Marines, they're ready for your assistance, sir.
هذان الجنديان من مشاة البحرية مستعدان لمساعدتك يا سيدي.
You two are Marines?
أنتما الاثنان من مشاة البحرية؟
Yes.
نعم.
Are you a Marine?
هل أنت جندي في مشاة البحرية؟
Exempted, but he was.
معفى، لكنه كان كذلك.
Oh!
أوه!
Salute!
تحية!
Hey, can you stop telling everyone my personal shit, man?
يا رجل، هل يمكنك التوقف عن إخبار الجميع بأموري الشخصية؟
This is how you get to know people.
هكذا تتعرف على الناس.
Put your hands down.
أنزل يديك.
What was your class?
ما هو صفك؟
Sit down.
اجلس.
You are my senior Marine!
أنت قائدي الأعلى في سلاح مشاة البحرية!
Are you really going to make me get up?
هل ستجبرني حقاً على النهوض؟
Now sit down.
اجلس الآن.
Once a Marine, always a Marine, sir!
من كان جنديًا في مشاة البحرية، يبقى جنديًا في مشاة البحرية إلى الأبد يا سيدي!
- Whoa! - Go easy on him.
- مهلاً! - خفف عنه.
This punk trying to one up on me.
هذا الوغد يحاول التفوق عليّ.
No, sir. It's the Marine spirit.
لا يا سيدي. إنها روح المارينز.
Uh, sir, he's just high on pride.
أجل يا سيدي، إنه متكبر للغاية.
If you could let him off the hook this one time.
لو سمحت له أن يفلت من العقاب هذه المرة.
"High on pride"?
"متغطرس"؟
Oh, uh, too much MCP, sir.
أوه، أه، لقد بالغت في استخدام برنامج MCP يا سيدي.
And what is that, huh?
وما هذا، هاه؟
- It's short for Marine Corps Pride. - Ah.
- إنه اختصار لعبارة "فخر سلاح مشاة البحرية". - آه.
What's your class?
ما هو صفك؟
He's high on MCP.
إنه تحت تأثير MCP.
Please tell me.
أرجوك أخبرني.
571. Happy?
571. هل أنت سعيد؟
Sir.
سيد.
Salute!
تحية!
And you?
وأنت؟
You think I can't put up a fight?
أتظن أنني لا أستطيع المقاومة؟
Mr. Choi might worry about you.
قد يقلق السيد تشوي عليك.
That's all.
هذا كل شيء.
I started this thing.
أنا من بدأ هذا الأمر.
I'm gonna end it.
سأنهي الأمر.
Okay.
تمام.
We strike tonight.
سنضرب الليلة.
Once you take down the sales director, you'll have to call me directly.
بمجرد أن تتخلص من مدير المبيعات، سيتعين عليك الاتصال بي مباشرة.
I'll be at the hospital.
سأكون في المستشفى.
Got it.
فهمتها.
Why do we have to wait to go in?
لماذا علينا الانتظار للدخول؟
If the director has goons protecting him, they're onto us.
إذا كان المخرج لديه رجال مسلحون يحمونه، فهم يعرفون أمرنا.
That means thugs are at the hospital.
هذا يعني أن المجرمين موجودون في المستشفى.
Isn't it dangerous for Du-yeong to go in alone?
أليس من الخطورة أن تدخل دو يونغ بمفردها؟
He's too fast for them.
إنه أسرع منهم بكثير.
Wouldn't it be safer if we all ganged up on Kim Jun-min,
ألن يكون الأمر أكثر أماناً لو تكاتفنا جميعاً ضد كيم جون مين؟
and went with him to the hospital?
وذهبت معه إلى المستشفى؟
Once they know that we're coming for them, it's going to be all hands on deck.
بمجرد أن يعلموا أننا قادمون إليهم، سيحتاج الجميع إلى التكاتف.
And we're dead.
ونحن أموات.
There's too many.
هناك الكثير جداً.
That's why we split up and hit at the same time.
لهذا السبب انقسمنا وضربنا في نفس الوقت.
- Mm-hm. - It's risky, but it's how we win this.
- هممم. - إنه أمر محفوف بالمخاطر، لكن هذه هي الطريقة التي سنفوز بها.
I'm on a motorcycle.
أنا على دراجة نارية.
I'll dip if it gets rough.
سأنسحب إذا اشتدت الأمور.
What do you think we should do?
ما رأيك فيما يجب أن نفعله؟
Can you ride a motorcycle?
هل تستطيع قيادة دراجة نارية؟
No.
لا.
They're way too fast.
إنهم سريعون للغاية.
What?
ماذا؟
Nothing, sir.
لا شيء يا سيدي.
I'll bring these guys with me.
سأحضر هؤلاء الرجال معي.
I may need help at the hospital.
قد أحتاج إلى مساعدة في المستشفى.
Okay.
تمام.
Then I'll go with Du-yeong, okay?
إذن سأختار دو-يونغ، حسناً؟
I'll bring my bike.
سأحضر دراجتي.
All right.
حسنًا.
Shall we have some food?
هل نتناول بعض الطعام؟
- Yeah.
- نعم نعم.
I didn't know you rode.
لم أكن أعلم أنك تركب الخيل.
- What kind?
- نعم. - أي نوع؟
I ride a naked bike.
أركب دراجة عارية.
Hey, we look kinda similar, yeah?
مهلاً، نحن متشابهان نوعاً ما، أليس كذلك؟
- Right? - Yeah.
- صحيح؟ - نعم.
Damn it.
عليك اللعنة.
Why are you mad? We look good.
لماذا أنت غاضب؟ نحن نبدو بمظهر جيد.
Where'd you serve, sir?
أين خدمت يا سيدي؟
Just leave it be.
اتركه وشأنه.
Stop it, man.
توقف عن ذلك يا رجل.
Hey, Min-dong.
مرحباً مين دونغ.
- Get some soup and rice. - Yes, sir.
- أحضر بعض الحساء والأرز. - حاضر سيدي.
Duk.
الجميع.
- How are you? - Oh, good. Been a while.
- كيف حالك؟ - بخير. لم أرك منذ مدة.
This is my friend.
هذا صديقي.
- Oh, hello. - Hi.
- أهلاً. - مرحباً.
I've already prepped.
لقد قمتُ بالتحضير مسبقاً.
The new ones are beautiful.
الجديدة جميلة.
- Have you ridden one? - Yeah, briefly a while back.
- هل ركبت واحدة من قبل؟ - نعم، لفترة وجيزة منذ فترة.
You're both Marines.
كلاكما من مشاة البحرية.
They taught you how to use knives, right?
لقد علموك كيفية استخدام السكاكين، أليس كذلك؟
- Try this. - Oh, no.
- جرب هذا. - أوه، لا.
They didn't?
ألم يفعلوا ذلك؟
- No.
- لا لا.
Then take these.
ثم خذ هذه.
Sir, are we… planning on using knives?
سيدي، هل نخطط لاستخدام السكاكين؟
- Did I just say that? - Well, you just offered them.
- هل قلت ذلك للتو؟ - حسناً، أنت من عرضتها عليهم.
I did.
فعلتُ.
I'm sorry, sir!
أنا آسف يا سيدي!
You need to know how to use a knife, so you can counter someone using one.
يجب أن تعرف كيفية استخدام السكين، حتى تتمكن من مواجهة شخص يستخدمها.
You need to know how they think.
عليك أن تعرف كيف يفكرون.
Oh.
أوه.
You scared me.
لقد أرعبتني.
Okay. This one's yours.
حسناً. هذا لك.
It's the fastest.
إنه الأسرع.
It suits you.
إنه يناسبك.
Sashimi knives don't have a guard between the hilt and blade.
لا تحتوي سكاكين الساشيمي على واقٍ بين المقبض والنصل.
Because it's not meant to stab.
لأنه ليس مصمماً للطعن.
Now, look. If you stab hard,
والآن، انظر. إذا طعنت بقوة،
your hand slides forward, and the blade fucks you up.
تنزلق يدك إلى الأمام، وتصيبك الشفرة بجروح بالغة.
If you want to stab with this,
إذا كنت تريد أن تطعن بهذا،
you need to support the end.
يجب عليك دعم النهاية.
And that…
وذلك...
…prevents slipping.
...يمنع الانزلاق.
If they come at you like this, what do you think they're going for?
إذا هاجموك بهذه الطريقة، فماذا تعتقد أنهم يسعون إليه؟
They're probably trying to slash your hand or wrist, sir.
ربما يحاولون قطع يدك أو معصمك يا سيدي.
That's right. Not a kill attack.
هذا صحيح. ليس هجومًا قاتلًا.
In boxing terms, it would be like throwing light jabs.
في مصطلحات الملاكمة، سيكون الأمر أشبه بتوجيه لكمات خفيفة.
- Mm-hm. - Ah.
- همم. - آه.
Once more! Keep it up.
مرة أخرى! استمروا على هذا المنوال.
Loosen up and keep circling.
استرخِ واستمر في الدوران.
And if they're supporting the hilt with both hands,
وإذا كانوا يمسكون المقبض بكلتا يديهم،
It's the kill.
إنها الضربة القاضية.
If you push down the knife with your thumb,
إذا ضغطت على السكين بإبهامك،
your hand won't slide unless there's a lot of force behind it.
لن تنزلق يدك إلا إذا كانت هناك قوة كبيرة وراءها.
If they're using this grip, it means they're experienced.
إذا كانوا يستخدمون هذه القبضة، فهذا يعني أنهم ذوو خبرة.
You're swinging like a bat.
أنت تتأرجح كالمضرب.
- So relax? - It's too much force.
- إذن اهدأ؟ - إنها قوة مفرطة.
- Uh-huh. - That's right.
- أجل. - هذا صحيح.
That's it!
هذا كل شيء!
- What the hell? Amazing. - Show me. Show me.
- يا إلهي! مذهل. - أرني. أرني.
Try to fuck with me, and I'll kill you.
حاول أن تعبث معي، وسأقتلك.
Deal the cards.
وزّع الأوراق.
- Fuck. Let me have this. - Hey, show me.
- اللعنة. دعني آخذ هذا. - هيا، أرني.
What's up, man?
كيف حالك يا رجل؟
You fucking pricks!
يا لكم من أوغاد!
We'll wait here.
سننتظر هنا.
Whoa, whoa!
مهلاً، مهلاً!
- Which apartment are you visiting? - 603.
- أي شقة تزور؟ - 603.
A car is coming.
سيارة قادمة.
There's a goon.
هناك بلطجي.
What now?
ماذا الآن؟
We'll wait.
سننتظر.
INCOMING CALL
مكالمة واردة
Damn it.
عليك اللعنة.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Now, listen.
والآن، استمع.
If you want to survive doing this work,
إذا كنت ترغب في البقاء على قيد الحياة من خلال القيام بهذا العمل،
you gotta sell everything.
عليك بيع كل شيء.
All of it.
كل ذلك.
Your fists, soul,
قبضتيك، روحك،
all of your dreams.
كل أحلامك.
But you can never sell out your friends and family.
لكن لا يمكنك أبداً أن تبيع أصدقاءك وعائلتك.
That's no way for you to live.
هذه ليست طريقة مناسبة للعيش.
- Yeah. - Yes.
- أجل. - نعم.
Once we're inside the hospital,
بمجرد دخولنا إلى المستشفى،
if I tell you guys to run, don't argue and just run.
إذا طلبت منكم أن تركضوا، فلا تجادلوا واركضوا فقط.
I'll take care of things myself.
سأعتني بالأمور بنفسي.
You hear me?
هل تسمعني؟
You just said not to abandon our friends or family, right, sir?
لقد قلت للتو ألا نتخلى عن أصدقائنا أو عائلاتنا، أليس كذلك يا سيدي؟
I'm a criminal.
أنا مجرم.
We may be in the same boat right now, but we're not a family, all right?
قد نكون في نفس الموقف الآن، لكننا لسنا عائلة، حسناً؟
We'll never meet again.
لن نلتقي مرة أخرى.
So don't get attached to any of this, okay?
لذا لا تتعلق بأي من هذا، حسناً؟
Understood?
مفهوم؟
Yeah.
نعم.
Kim Jun-min is here.
كيم جون مين هنا.
What should we do?
ماذا يجب أن نفعل؟
Mr. Lee, what do we do?
سيد لي، ماذا نفعل؟
Can you hear me?
أيمكنك سماعي؟
- Just answer me. - It's a go.
- أجبني فقط. - موافق.
Ah, shit. This asshole!
يا إلهي! هذا الأحمق!
- Fuck! - Call the hospital, idiot!
- اللعنة! - اتصل بالمستشفى أيها الأحمق!
You son of a bitch!
يا ابن العاهرة!
- You motherfucker! - Die, asshole.
- يا ابن العاهرة! - مت أيها الوغد.
Do-hu, put this asshole in the trunk.
دو-هو، ضع هذا الأحمق في صندوق السيارة.
Get him up!
أيقظه!
What the hell?
بحق الجحيم؟
Who is that fucker?!
من هذا الوغد؟!
Fuck!
اللعنة!
Hey! Whoa, whoa!
مهلاً! مهلاً، مهلاً!
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
MAIN BUILDING PATIENT ROOM, BLOCK 17
غرفة المرضى في المبنى الرئيسي ، المبنى رقم 17
DU-YEONG
يو يونغ
What's up?
ما أخبارك؟
You all right?
هل أنت بخير؟
Okay.
تمام.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
- Okay. - Yes, sir.
- حسناً. - نعم سيدي.
That was Im Jang-do.
كان ذلك إم جانغ-دو.
BITCOIN
بيتكوين
That's right, up you go.
هذا صحيح، هيا اصعد.
Damn it!
عليك اللعنة!
I know. We're just--
أعلم. نحن فقط...
Hold on.
يتمسك.
Damn it!
عليك اللعنة!
The hell?
ما هذا بحق الجحيم؟
- Let's go. - Okay.
- هيا بنا. - حسناً.
- Careful.
- انتبه.
WE'VE GOT IM JANG-DO TAKING HIM TO DU-YEONG'S STORE
لدينا إم جانغ دو وهو يأخذه إلى متجر دو يونغ
Gentlemen.
السادة المحترمون.
- Hello.
- مرحباً.
Put him in that.
ضعه في ذلك.
Yes.
نعم.
One, two…
واحد، اثنان…
Careful with him.
احذر منه.
Where's the salt?
أين الملح؟
Salt?
ملح؟
In the office.
في المكتب.
Go make some salt water.
اصنع بعض الماء المالح.
Find a bucket, dump it in.
ابحث عن دلو، ثم أفرغه فيه.
Okay.
تمام.
- Let's go. - All right.
- هيا بنا. - حسناً.
In the corner.
في الزاوية.
- Okay. - Yes.
- نعم.
Hyeon-ju, you okay?
هيون جو، هل أنتِ بخير؟
Yeah, are you all right?
نعم، هل أنت بخير؟
Mm-hm.
ممم.
We got Im Jang-do.
لقد حصلنا على إم جانغ-دو.
- Mm-hm. - What about you?
- هممم. - ماذا عنك؟
Uh, I was outside, but Du-yeong got him.
كنت بالخارج، لكن دو يونغ أمسك به.
- Oh. - He killed him?
- أوه. - هل قتله؟
Let's go make the salt water.
هيا بنا نحضر الماء المالح.
- Come on. - Uh-huh.
- هيا. - أوه-هاه.
We can use this.
يمكننا استخدام هذا.
- Water? - I think I saw it downstairs.
- ماء؟ - أعتقد أنني رأيته في الطابق السفلي.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Hyeon-ju, come on.
هيون جو، هيا.
Yeah?
نعم؟
I'll be there in five minutes, so shake him up a little.
سأكون هناك خلال خمس دقائق، لذا هزه قليلاً.
Oh, and… have Hyeon-ju and the guys watch.
أوه، و... دعوا هيون جو والشباب يشاهدون.
What's up?
ما أخبارك؟
He told me to have Hyeon-ju watch.
طلب مني أن أجعل هيون جو يراقب.
Why?
لماذا؟
I hope she can take it.
أتمنى أن تتمكن من تحمل ذلك.
Hello, sir. This way.
مرحباً سيدي. تفضل من هنا.
Stop. Now show us the stairs.
توقف. الآن أرنا الدرج.
We don't have cameras on that side.
لا توجد كاميرات على ذلك الجانب.
Why not?
ولم لا؟
We just don't.
لا نفعل ذلك ببساطة.
Are you kidding me? You shit--
هل تمزح معي؟ يا لك من حقير!
So, tell me something.
إذن، أخبرني شيئاً.
Are there any cameras facing the building?
هل توجد أي كاميرات مراقبة موجهة نحو المبنى؟
The police would probably have some.
من المحتمل أن يكون لدى الشرطة بعضها.
How's Jun-min?
كيف حال جون مين؟
He's still unconscious.
لا يزال فاقداً للوعي.
Go to the management office
اذهب إلى مكتب الإدارة
and get the plates of the fuckers who attacked him.
واحصل على لوحات أرقام هواتف الأوغاد الذين اعتدوا عليه.
Yes.
نعم.
Right there, man.
هذا هو بالضبط يا رجل.
How much do we pour in?
كم ننفق؟
Uh, didn't he tell us to use it all?
ألم يطلب منا أن نستخدمها كلها؟
It's a lot.
إنه كثير.
Let's put it all in. I guess that's what he wants.
لنضع كل شيء في الاعتبار. أعتقد أن هذا ما يريده.
Okay.
تمام.
But why?
لكن لماذا؟
Making salt water.
تحضير الماء المالح.
Bring it here.
أحضره إلى هنا.
Uh, yes.
أجل، صحيح.
Sit down and watch.
اجلس وشاهد.
Why?
لماذا؟
Mr. Choi's orders.
أوامر السيد تشوي.
My pet peeve is people not talking when they say they're going to.
أكثر ما يزعجني هو عدم التزام الناس بالوعد الذي قطعوه على أنفسهم.
That means you'll nod your head only when you have something to say to us.
هذا يعني أنك ستومئ برأسك فقط عندما يكون لديك شيء لتقوله لنا.
Because if you nod and don't talk, I promise I will cut your lips off.
لأنك إذا أومأت برأسك ولم تتكلم، أعدك أنني سأقطع شفتيك.
Got it?
فهمتها؟
You don't want to talk?
ألا تريد التحدث؟
Hyeon-ju.
هيون جو.
Why did you make me watch?
لماذا أجبرتني على المشاهدة؟
Myeong-gil has probably started looking for Im Jang-do by now.
ربما يكون ميونغ غيل قد بدأ البحث عن إم جانغ دو الآن.
We don't have much time.
ليس لدينا الكثير من الوقت.
You watched because I wanted you guys to know something.
لقد شاهدتموني لأنني أردت أن تعرفوا شيئاً ما.
What are you talking about?
عن ماذا تتحدث؟
This is not going to end until someone dies.
لن ينتهي هذا الأمر حتى يموت أحدهم.
And there's no guarantee that someone won't be me.
وليس هناك ما يضمن ألا أكون أنا الشخص الذي سيحدث له ذلك.
Why would you say something so horrible?
لماذا تقول شيئًا فظيعًا كهذا؟
- Hyeon-ju. - That's enough.
- هيون جو. - هذا يكفي.
Hyeon-ju!
هيون جو!
Mr. Oh, look after her.
السيد أوه، اعتني بها.
Yes, sir.
نعم سيدي.
Oh, goddammit, that kid.
يا إلهي، ذلك الطفل!
- Gun-woo. - Uh, yes.
- غون وو. - آه، نعم.
If you end up…
إذا انتهى بك الأمر...
fighting Myeong-gil,
قتال ميونغ غيل،
can you protect the others?
هل يمكنك حماية الآخرين؟
Will you please do that for me?
هل يمكنك أن تفعل ذلك من أجلي؟
With all of my will, sir.
بكل إرادتي يا سيدي.
Thank you so much.
شكراً جزيلاً.
We don't have much time.
ليس لدينا الكثير من الوقت.
Let me teach you just one thing now.
دعني أعلمك شيئًا واحدًا فقط الآن.
In order to take down an organization, all you need is
لإسقاط أي منظمة، كل ما تحتاجه هو
dispersion and division.
التشتت والانقسام.
People tend to trust those that know and empathize with them.
يميل الناس إلى الثقة بمن يعرفونهم ويتعاطفون معهم.
If you're not able to gain their trust,
إذا لم تتمكن من كسب ثقتهم،
your organization can be divided.
يمكن تقسيم مؤسستك.
Take that off.
انزع ذلك.
Im Jang-do?
إم جانغ دو؟
I've been led to believe that you
لقد تم إيهامي بأنك
may be the one who understands Myeong-gil the best of all his men.
ربما يكون هو الشخص الذي يفهم ميونغ غيل أفضل من بين جميع رجاله.
Myeong-gil is a very violent, cruel man.
ميونغ غيل رجل عنيف وقاسٍ للغاية.
But he's capable of reading people like a book.
لكنه قادر على قراءة الناس كالكتاب المفتوح.
He truly gets them.
إنه يفهمهم حقاً.
I'm sure plenty of his men take him at his word.
أنا متأكد من أن الكثير من رجاله يصدقونه.
But you're smarter.
لكنك أذكى.
You know Myeong-gil.
أنت تعرف شارع ميونغ غيل.
You know he doesn't ever empathize with any one of his people.
أنت تعلم أنه لا يتعاطف أبداً مع أي فرد من شعبه.
He's cold and calculating.
إنه بارد وحسابي.
Always thinking how best to move his little pieces to his advantage.
يفكر دائماً في أفضل طريقة لتحريك قطعه الصغيرة لصالحه.
You knew all this, and you still decided to work for him.
كنت تعلم كل هذا، ومع ذلك قررت العمل لديه.
Why?
لماذا؟
At first, you were just led by greed.
في البداية، كنتَ مُقاداً بالجشع فحسب.
In only one year,
في عام واحد فقط،
he paid you what a major corporate gig would have paid in five.
لقد دفع لك ما كان سيدفعه لك عملٌ كبير في شركة كبرى في غضون خمسة أشهر.
Graduating from the Police Academy was supposed to give you authority,
كان من المفترض أن يمنحك التخرج من أكاديمية الشرطة سلطة،
but you ended up getting yourself demoted.
لكن انتهى بك الأمر إلى تخفيض رتبتك.
It was all about your pride.
كان الأمر كله يتعلق بكبريائك.
I suppose that pride was the real reason you were fine working for him after all.
أظن أن ذلك الكبرياء كان السبب الحقيقي وراء رضاك ​​بالعمل معه في نهاية المطاف.
You were confident that you could keep your sense of agency.
كنت واثقاً من قدرتك على الحفاظ على إحساسك بالسيطرة على زمام الأمور.
You'd never lose that.
لن تخسر ذلك أبداً.
Not to a low-life thug.
ليس لبلطجي وضيع.
And if by chance he found some reason to kill you,
وإذا وجد بالصدفة سبباً ما لقتلك،
you could just run off
يمكنك ببساطة أن تهرب
with the money you made working for him.
بالمال الذي جنيته من العمل لديه.
Hm, I like that plan.
همم، تعجبني هذه الخطة.
If I took your photo and decided to sent it to him right now
لو أنني التقطت صورتك وقررت إرسالها إليه الآن
and said that you gave me the names of the people he had you kill,
وقال إنك أعطيتني أسماء الأشخاص الذين أمرك بقتلهم.
he would surely believe me over you.
سيصدقني بالتأكيد أكثر منك.
After all, what man wouldn't squeal if they were in your current position?
في النهاية، أي رجل لن يصرخ لو كان مكانك الحالي؟
Then he'd call back all the men he sent out to find you…
ثم سيستدعي جميع الرجال الذين أرسلهم للبحث عنك...
…unleash a pack of bloodhounds,
...أطلق العنان لمجموعة من كلاب الصيد،
and they'll kill you in no time.
وسوف يقتلونك في لمح البصر.
You wouldn't even get a chance to plead your case.
لن تحصل حتى على فرصة لعرض قضيتك.
He won't let you.
لن يسمح لك بذلك.
Myeong-gil doesn't care about the truth.
لا يهتم ميونغ غيل بالحقيقة.
The math tells him to bury you.
تشير الحسابات إلى أنه يجب عليه دفنك.
I mean, if there is one person on the planet
أعني، إذا كان هناك شخص واحد على هذا الكوكب
who knows every single one of Myeong-gil's crimes,
من يعرف كل جريمة من جرائم ميونغ غيل؟
that person is you, isn't it?
هذا الشخص هو أنت، أليس كذلك؟
You know him just as well as I do.
أنت تعرفه جيداً مثلي تماماً.
If I plant even the smallest seed of doubt about you to Myeong-gil…
إذا زرعتُ ولو بذرة شك صغيرة فيك لدى ميونغ غيل...
you are a dead man.
أنت رجل ميت.
Fuck.
اللعنة.
Wait. Damn it.
انتظر. اللعنة.
Why should I die?!
لماذا يجب أن أموت؟!
Fuck me!
اللعنة علي!
Im Jang-do!
إم جانغ-دو!
Shut up and listen to me!
اصمت واستمع إلي!
If you don't pull yourself together, you will die.
إذا لم تتماسك، فسوف تموت.
Tell me everything.
أخبرني بكل شيء.
And I will send you to a safe country far away from here
وسأرسلكم إلى بلد آمن بعيد عن هنا
with more than enough money to live.
مع وجود ما يكفي من المال للعيش.
I taught Myeong-gil everything.
لقد علّمت ميونغ غيل كل شيء.
I know of places that he hasn't even heard of.
أعرف أماكن لم يسمع بها حتى.
This is a promise.
هذا وعد.
You were already planning to leave sooner or later.
كنت تخطط بالفعل للمغادرة عاجلاً أم آجلاً.
I'm giving you the chance to do it.
أنا أمنحك الفرصة للقيام بذلك.
If I talk,
إذا تكلمت،
how much money?
كم من المال؟
I'd answer quickly if I were you.,
لو كنت مكانك لأجبت بسرعة.
Myeong-gil and Smile Capital are going down for good.
ستنهار شركة ميونغ غيل وشركة سمايل كابيتال إلى الأبد.
After that, you're in Guam.
بعد ذلك، ستكون في غوام.
I know some people there.
أعرف بعض الأشخاص هناك.
You'll have plenty enough to start a new life.
سيكون لديك ما يكفي لبدء حياة جديدة.
Get him some clothes.
أحضر له بعض الملابس.
How long have you worked for him?
كم من الوقت وأنت تعمل لديه؟
Five years.
خمس سنوات.
And what is it you do exactly?
وماذا تفعل بالضبط؟
I ensure Mr. Kim's illegal dealings fly under police radar
أضمن أن تبقى تعاملات السيد كيم غير القانونية بعيدة عن أنظار الشرطة.
and make sure things run smoothly if the police do sniff around.
وتأكد من سير الأمور بسلاسة إذا قامت الشرطة بالتفتيش.
All right, but what did you do?
حسناً، ولكن ماذا فعلت؟
For small stuff, me and In-beom handled it.
أما بالنسبة للأمور الصغيرة، فقد توليتها أنا وإن-بيوم.
And for bigger things, we used Kim's service company.
أما بالنسبة للأمور الأكبر، فقد استعنّا بشركة خدمات كيم.
What small stuff?
ما هي الأشياء الصغيرة؟
Like…
يحب…
…filming things to use against people.
...تصوير أشياء لاستخدامها ضد الناس.
You threatened Iil Group, am I right?
لقد هددت مجموعة إيل، أليس كذلك؟
Tell me.
أخبرني.
Look, Mr. Kim made me do it.
انظر، لقد أجبرني السيد كيم على فعل ذلك.
He didn't ask you who made you do it. He asked you what you did.
لم يسألك من الذي أجبرك على فعل ذلك. بل سألك ماذا فعلت.
I gathered some footage of the Iil Group heir.
لقد جمعت بعض اللقطات المصورة لوريث مجموعة إيل.
And?
و؟
We just… We stripped him.
لقد جردناه من ملابسه فحسب... لقد جردناه من ملابسه.
Why?
لماذا؟
Tell me everything from the start.
أخبرني بكل شيء منذ البداية.
There was a 40-story boutique hotel being built in Gangnam,
كان يجري بناء فندق بوتيكي مكون من 40 طابقاً في غانغنام،
but the company went bankrupt during the pandemic.
لكن الشركة أفلست خلال فترة الجائحة.
Mr. Kim got wind of intel
علم السيد كيم بالمعلومات الاستخباراتية
that the Iil Group heir was going to take over the hotel project.
أن وريث مجموعة إيل كان سيتولى مشروع الفندق.
But from whom?
لكن ممن؟
The hotel became an eyesore, so Seoul City decided to step in.
أصبح الفندق مشهداً قبيحاً، لذلك قررت مدينة سيول التدخل.
They were looking for someone with cash.
كانوا يبحثون عن شخص لديه نقود.
An assemblyman who plays golf with Mr. Kim recommended him to the mayor.
أوصى أحد أعضاء المجلس التشريعي الذي يلعب الغولف مع السيد كيم به إلى رئيس البلدية.
He wants the… hotel to become a casino.
يريد أن يتحول الفندق إلى كازينو.
Seoul City said they'd grant him a permit for it.
أعلنت مدينة سيول أنها ستمنحه تصريحاً بذلك.
Mr. Kim got excited.
انتاب السيد كيم شعور بالحماس.
But the Iil Group heir tried to back out,
لكن وريث مجموعة إيل حاول التراجع،
so I forced him to cooperate.
لذلك أجبرته على التعاون.
How many people have you taken videos of?
كم عدد الأشخاص الذين قمت بتصويرهم؟
Fifty.
خمسون.
And Myeong-gil still has all of them?
وهل لا يزال ميونغ غيل يحتفظ بهم جميعاً؟
Yeah.
نعم.
He sees people's weakness as a source of income.
إنه ينظر إلى ضعف الناس كمصدر للدخل.
He never gets rid of anything that's of value to him.
إنه لا يتخلص أبداً من أي شيء ذي قيمة بالنسبة له.
Where does he keep these videos?
أين يحتفظ بهذه الفيديوهات؟
He keeps an encrypted hard drive in a safe inside his bedroom.
يحتفظ بقرص صلب مشفر في خزنة داخل غرفة نومه.
But it's this German smart safe.
لكنها خزنة ذكية ألمانية.
It has a biometric lock.
يحتوي على قفل بيومتري.
And if he knows there are any issues arising,
وإذا علم بوجود أي مشاكل ناشئة،
he can incinerate everything inside it.
بإمكانه أن يحرق كل شيء بداخله.
He can press a button on his phone,
بإمكانه الضغط على زر في هاتفه،
and this thing will burn its contents.
وهذا الشيء سيحرق محتوياته.
Nothing left.
لم يتبق شيء.
He knows that this is a double-edged sword.
هو يعلم أن هذا سلاح ذو حدين.
A weapon in his hands but evidence for the police.
سلاح في يديه، لكنه دليل للشرطة.
The service company, is it a gang?
هل شركة الخدمات هذه عصابة؟
Yeah.
نعم.
How big?
ما حجمها؟
I believe it's around 30, but they can get more.
أعتقد أن العدد حوالي 30، لكن بإمكانهم الحصول على المزيد.
And who runs it?
ومن يديره؟
It's Mr. Jung.
إنه السيد يونغ.
He's basically Mr. Kim's guard dog.
هو في الأساس كلب حراسة السيد كيم.
He was an MMA fighter,
كان مقاتلاً في فنون القتال المختلطة (MMA).
but apparently he was banned for beating a man to death in the octagon.
لكن يبدو أنه تم منعه بسبب ضربه رجلاً حتى الموت في الحلبة الثمانية الأضلاع.
That's when he was recruited.
في ذلك الوقت تم تجنيده.
Who handles the bodies?
من يتولى أمر الجثث؟
Mr. Jung takes care of that.
السيد جونغ يتولى الأمر.
Tell me everything you know.
أخبرني بكل ما تعرفه.
Three years ago,
قبل ثلاث سنوات،
Mr. Kim had a bit too much to drink and killed a man with his bare hands.
تناول السيد كيم كمية كبيرة من الكحول وقتل رجلاً بيديه العاريتين.
I was nearby at the time,
كنتُ قريباً في ذلك الوقت،
so I handled the scene until Mr. Jung arrived.
لذا توليت إدارة الموقف حتى وصل السيد جونغ.
He called a 3-ton fish truck with an aquarium
اتصل بشاحنة أسماك وزنها 3 أطنان مزودة بحوض أسماك
and carried the body away.
وحملوا الجثة بعيداً.
From the way he spoke to the driver, it seemed like he did this a lot.
من طريقة حديثه مع السائق، بدا أنه يفعل ذلك كثيراً.
The name?
الاسم؟
I don't remember the name.
لا أتذكر الاسم.
I see.
أرى.
I know a hospital in Incheon.
أعرف مستشفى في إنتشون.
I'll call an ambulance, and you'll get some rest.
سأتصل بالإسعاف، وستحصل على بعض الراحة.
Once everything is over,
بمجرد انتهاء كل شيء،
I'll arrange a flight and ID for you.
سأرتب لك رحلة طيران وبطاقة هوية.
Do not try to contact anyone.
لا تحاول الاتصال بأي شخص.
Otherwise, he'll find you.
وإلا، فسوف يجدك.
Your phone. I'm keeping it.
هاتفك. سأحتفظ به.
Let me ask you one last thing.
دعني أسألك سؤالاً أخيراً.
Where does he keep his gold stashed?
أين يخبئ ذهبه؟
Only In-beom knows.
لا أحد يعلم سوى إن-بيوم.
Tell me why that is.
أخبرني لماذا.
In-beom is the only person Mr. Kim trusts.
إن-بيوم هو الشخص الوحيد الذي يثق به السيد كيم.
They met in prison.
التقيا في السجن.
and they've saved each other's lives multiple times.
وقد أنقذ كل منهما حياة الآخر عدة مرات.
In-beom would give his life for him.
إن-بيوم سيضحي بحياته من أجله.
I don't know everything Mr. Kim is thinking,
لا أعرف كل ما يفكر فيه السيد كيم،
but I know In-beom is like a brother.
لكنني أعرف أن إن-بيوم بمثابة أخي.